# JENNIE GONG

022 328 1286 xinning.gong@gmail.com https://jenniegong.vercel.app/

#### **PERSONAL PROFILE**

I am a hard-working, curious and self-motivated person with a passion for IT. I love analysing data and problem solving as I find connecting information and forming relationships fascinating. I have studied a myriad of coding languages for 6 years and have completed many personal and academic projects. I am adaptable and a quick learner. For example, I learnt to create a google chrome extension and use typescript at a hackathon within 2 hours. I am able to work effectively independently and with a team.

#### **SKILLS AND STRENGTHS**

- R Use R Markdown to model and analyse data, ggplot2, web scraping, data wrangling, random forest, bootstrapping
- Database MySQL, SQLite, PHP, Amazon cloud services, Microsoft SQL server.
- Python 6 years: recursive algorithms, data structures, functions, classes, debugging, abstract data types.
- **Java** OO Programming and Design, frameworks.
- Excel linear programming problems, pivot tables, data entry and analytics
- Front end web dev- multiple page dynamic, responsive website with database
- JavaScript created a hangman app, jQuery 3.3.1 to create webpage
- Design Photoshop, Canva, Adobe XD and powerpoint
- Websphere process modelling
- ER Modelling, project proposal, data modelling, normalisation, json, XML

# PROJECTS AND EXPERIENCE

# **Reddit Webapp and Chrome Extension**

WDCC x SESA Hackathon | 2021

- Built webapp that looks like VS code using reddit API and displayed posts as code for the theme of procrastination
- Created google chrome extension to allow easy access to webapp using json and javascript
- Created presentation and promotional video
- Received best design award for demonstrating excellence in UI/UX design

# **Statistical Modelling**

# UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND ASSIGNMENT | 2021

- Study on the effect of insulin on mice and predicting oxygen consumption in humans using simulation based procedures e.g bootstrapping and cross-validation
- Generalised linear models and related methods
- Provide robust inference, investigate consequences of assumption violation and conclusions
- Perform goodness of fit and model selection

# Webportal with project proposal and deliverable

UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND GROUP PROJECT | 2020

- Develop a business proposal to create web portal for a career agency with use case models, functions outline, prototype documentation, test plan and design principles.
- Use AdobeXD to create multiple GUI prototypes for different device types.
- Presentation of project to stakeholders and project manager.
- Received A grade for overall project.

# **EDUCATION**

# University of Auckland

MAR 2020 - PRESENT

Bachelor of Science, majoring in Statistics and Information Technology Management (Expected graduation Nov 2022)

Papers: Computer Science, Information Systems, Business Analysis, Statistics, Engineering Science, Operations Management

# **Massey University**

FEB 2019 - NOV 2019

Certificate of Proficiency Undergraduate

#### OTHER EXPERIENCE

- Mentee at Cisco MentorMe
   2021 Programme
- Alpha Tester for Fist Bump a startup aimed to connect students using an algorithm
- Summer internship for IT, marketing and teaching English in Nanjing, China 2019-2020
- Waitress at Goan Korean BBQ Restaurant and Hana Mizu Ki Restaurant 2018-2019

# EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- UoA Class Rep
- UoA Information System and Business Analytics Society
- UoA Web Development & Consulting Club
- UoA Developers Society
- UoA Google Developer Student Club
- Beta Alpha Sci
- Auckland Student Pool Association
- UoA Kiwi Asian Club
- Auckland University Chinese Student Society
- UoA Kpop Planet
- VEX Robotics
- NZ UN Youth
- Youth Judge at the Manawatu Science Fair
- PNGHS academic tutor

#### **WEBSITES**

## Linkedin:

www.linkedin.com/in/jenniegong

## **GitHub:**

https://github.com/xinninggong

#### REFEREES

#### **David Smith**

Professional Teaching Fellow University of Auckland

# Lucy Eberhardt

Marketing Manager The Plaza Shopping Centre

Out of courtesy to my referees, details are available on request.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **Teaching Assistant**

# UNIVERSITY OF AUCKLAND | MAR 2021 - PRESENT

- Mark assessments and record data entry associated with marks in appropriate university systems
- Summarise common student errors and areas of improvement for individual students

# Sales and Services Assistant

FARMERS PALMERSTON NORTH | 2020 - 2021

- Processed sales, exchanges, customer orders and stock transfers using POS system
- Troubleshoot and assist the security and sales team with technical issues
- Assist customers with queries and purchasing decisions

### **Promotions Assistant**

## THE PLAZA SHOPPING CENTRE | 2017 - 2019

- Assist in promoting and marketing events
- Handling customers and general enquiries
- Opening, cleaning and closing down booths
- Running activities and supervising children

# **AWARDS AND ACHIEVEMENTS**

#### 2021

• WDCC x SESA Hackathon Best Design Award

# Commitment and Leadership as UoA Class Representative

#### 2020

 UoA Certificate of Outstanding Achievement in Computer Science

### UoA Certificate of Distinction in Statistics

• Certificate of Achievement for

#### Prior to 2020

- Placed second at AgTech Hackathon with web app to optimise kiwifruit production
- Attended NanoCamp in Canterbury University for top NZ science students
- Langley Memorial Prize Manawatu Science Fair
- Fonterra High Distinction at Manawatu Science Fair
- Bronze CREST
- High school Prefect Award
- High Distinction in NCSS challenge Intermediate category

- UOA Academic Potential Scholarship
- Course Distinction Award NCEA Level 3 English, Statistics and Accounting with first place in Statistics and Accounting
- PNGHS Gifted and Talented programme
- Elite Award for Education
   Perfect Maths placing in the top
   100 globally
- Laureate for Music achieving Grade 8 piano with merit
- Bronze Award Chamber Music placing in the top 30 nationally